Inventaris van het Archief van de Raad voor de Scheepvaart (1908) 1909-2010
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Bijzonder, B.
  - Taakuitvoering, B.2
    - Onderzoek scheepsongevallen, B.2.7
      - Ter documentatie aangeschafte Zeekaarten, B.2.7.3
        - British Admiralty Charts, B.2.7.3.2
          - Atlantic Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.1
            - Coastal waters west coast Europe, B.2.7.3.2.1.5
              - 2548: Ria de Vigo, 28th September 1915, 2605; blad
              - 2641: Pertuis Breton, 16th October 1953 (last correction 1960), 2606; blad
              - 2645: Ile de Groix to Raz de Sein, 2nd May 1859 (last correction 1948), 2607; blad
              - 2646: Bourgneuf to Ile de Groix, 2nd May 1858 (last correction 1933), 2608; blad
              - 2646: Bourgneuf to Ile de Groix, 2nd May 1858 (last correction 1950), 2609; blad
              - 2647: Les Sables d'Olonne to Bourgneuf, 6th June 1859 (last correction 1950), 2610; blad
              - 2647: Les Sables d'Olonne to Bourgneuf, 6th June 1859 (last correction 1962), 2611; blad
              - 2648: Pte. de la Coubre to Les Sables d'Olonne, 3rd March 1944 (revised 1961), 2612; blad
              - 2664: Pointe d'Arcachon to Pointe de la Coubre, 5th November 1954, 2613; blad
              - 2664: Pointe d'Arcachon to Pointe de la Coubre, 5th November 1954 (last correction 1957), 2614; blad
              - 2665: Rio Bidasoa to Pointe d'Arcachon, 14th June 1859 (last correction 1952), 2615; blad
              - 2690: Cap de la Chèvre to Pointe de Corsen including Rade de Brest, 15th July 1859 (revised 1962), 2616; blad
              - 2694: The channels between Ushant and the mainland, 23rd January 1860 (last correction 1959), 2617; blad
              - 2746: Pertuis d'Antioche with the approaches to La Rochelle and Rochefort, 8th May 1953, 2618; blad
              - 2925: San Sebastian to Santander, 6th April 1934 (last correction 1952), 2619; blad
              - 2925: San Sebastian to Santander, 6th April 1934 (last correction 1957), 2620; blad
              - 2926: Santander to Gijon, 26th June 1933 (last correction 1952), 2621; blad
              - 2926: Santander to Gijon, 26th June 1933 (last correction 1956), 2622; blad
              - 2927: Gijon to Foz, 24th March 1933 (last correction 1952), 2623; blad
              - 2927: Gijon to Foz, 24th March 1933 (last correction 1956), 2624; blad
              - 3263: Approaches to Lisbon, 13th March 1964, 2625; blad
              - 3264: Port of Lisbon, 13th March 1964, 2626; blad
              - 3764: Cabo Toriñana to Punta Carreiro, 11th July 1911 (last correction 1929), 2627; blad
            - North Atlantic Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.1.6
              - 11a: Gnomonic chart - North Atlantic Ocean, 12th January 1914 (last correction 1937), 2628; blad
              - 365: Ilheus Selvagem, 15th May 1942 (last correction 1951), 2629; blad
              - 366: Arquipélago de Cabo Verde, 9th June 1944 (last correction 1955), 2630; blad
              - 369: Plans in the Arquipélago de Cabo Verde, 30th September 1895 (last correction 1957), 2631; blad
              - 370: Porto Grande, 9th September 1874 (revised 1962), 2632; blad
              - 565: Iceland, 27th June 1941 (last correction 1960), 2633; blad
              - 1077a: Steamship routes Atlantic Ocean, 8th February 1935 (last correction 1938), 2634; blad
              - 1127: Outer approaches to the North Channel, 21st December 1979 (last correction 1992), 2635; blad
              - 1831: Arquipelago da Madeira, 28th January 1944 (last correction 1948), 2636; blad
              - 1854: Plans in the Arquipélago dos Açores, 8th March 1957, 2637; blad
              - 1855: Fayal Pico and San Jorge, 25th July 1849 (last correction 1956), 2638; blad
              - 1856: Plans in the Islas Canarias, 1st November 1963, 2639; blad
              - 1865: Ilha de Santa Maria - Baia de S. Lourenço - Vila do Porto, 26th October 1956, 2640; blad
              - 1869: Gran Canaria to Hierro, 30th December 1940 (revised 1962), 2641; blad
              - 1870: Lanzarote to Gran Canaria, 30th December 1940 (last correction 1954), 2642; blad
              - 1940: Canal do Faial - Porto da Horta, 13th July 1956, 2643; blad
              - 1946: Corvo and Flores, 18th July 1849 (last correction 1956), 2644; blad
              - 1950: Arquipélago dos Açores, 28th July 1961, 2645; blad
              - 2058c: North Atlantic Route Chart - Lane routes north of Ireland, 19th March 1937 (last correction 1955), 2646; blad
              - 2059: North Atlantic Ocean, 9th August 1883 (revised 1960), 2647; blad
              - 2060a: North Atlantic Ocean - eastern portion, 1st November 1870 (last correction 1955), 2648; blad
              - 2060b: North Atlantic Ocean - western portion, 1st November 1870 (revised 1960), 2649; blad
              - 2282: The Greenland and Barents Sea, 26th August 1872 (revised 1960), 2650; blad
              - 2733: Dyrhólaey to Snaefellsjökull including Faxaflói, 25th May 1956 (last correction 1959), 2651; blad
              - 2867: Plans in the North Pacific Ocean, 17th August 1951 (revised 1959), 2652; blad
              - 3201: Hafnarfjödr and Reykjavik and approaches - Reykjavik Habour, 8th July 1908 (last correction 1960), 2653; blad
              - 3273: The West Indies, 31st January 1903 (revised 1960), 2654; blad
              - 3557: Plans in the Faeroes, 27th June 1958, 2655; blad
              - 3848: Lisbon to Freetown, 21st April 1967, 2656; blad
              - 4014: North Atlantic Ocean eastern part, 19th December 1975 (revised 1984) (last correction 1991), 2657; blad
            - South Atlantic Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.1.7
              - 388: Islands in the South Atlantic Ocean, 15th January 1913 (revised 1961), 2658; blad
              - 1691: Island of Ascension, 18th January 1910 (revised 1962), 2659; blad
              - 1769: Islands and anchorages in the South Atlantic Ocean, 29th September 1922 (revised 1963), 2660; blad
              - 1771: Saint Helena, 4th May 1922 (last correction 1955), 2661; blad
              - 2127: Atlantic Ocean, 10th June 1927 (last correction 1949), 2662; blad
              - 2127: Atlantic Ocean, 10th June 1927 (revised 1967), 2663; blad
              - 2202a: South Atlantic Ocean - eastern portion, 13th February 1871 (revised 1960), 2664; blad
              - 2202b: South Atlantic Ocean - western portion, 13th February 1871 (revised 1960), 2665; blad
          - Indian Ocean, B.2.7.3.2.2
            - Arabian Sea, Laccadive Sea, B.2.7.3.2.2.1
              - 5: Sokótra, 1st August 1835 (last correction 1955), 2666; blad
              - 38: Muscat to Karachi, 31st December 1874 (last correction 1956), 2667; blad
              - 39: Coasts of Sind and Kutch, 11th May 1915 (last correction 1956), 2668; blad
              - 40: Karachi Harbour, 5th May 1961, 2669; blad
              - 41: The Swatch to Cape Monze, 13th January 1956, 2670; blad
              - 43: Gulf of Kutch, 19th October 1956, 2671; blad
              - 47: Okha Port (Beyt Harbour) and approaches, 10th December 1927 (last correction 1956), 2672; blad
              - 51: Gulf of Cambay, 28th December 1934 (last correction 1963), 2673; blad
              - 61: Approaches to Karachi, 15th October 1954 (last correction 1956), 2674; blad
              - 64: Sacrifice Rock to Beypore, 8th October 1888 (last correction 1961), 2675; blad
              - 65: Approaches to Cochin, 30th August 1963, 2676; blad
              - 67: Approaches to Tuticorin, 4th November 1960, 2677; blad
              - 68a: Palk Strait and Gulf of Mannar - northern sheet, 16th November 1931 (last correction 1956), 2678; blad
              - 68b: Palk Strait and Gulf of Mannar - southern sheet, 1st July 1862 (last correction 1958), 2679; blad
              - 118: Kediwari Mouth to Nirani Creek, 27th November 1897 (last correction 1955), 2680; blad
              - 145: Plans on Makran Coast - Hor Rabij and Jask Bay, 12th June 1912 (last correction 1951), 2681; blad
              - 655: Port of Bombay, 12th September 1958 (revised 1960), 2682; blad
              - 735: Surat Roads to Maroli, 20th August 1857 (last correction 1955), 2683; blad
              - 736: Maroli to Arnala Island, 20th August 1857 (last correction 1953), 2684; blad
              - 737: Arnala Island to Khanderi Island, 12th October 1920 (last correction 1956), 2685; blad
              - 738: Khanderi Island to Boria Pagoda, 19th April 1910 (last correction 1954), 2686; blad
              - 739: Boria Pagoda to Malvan, 10th October 1912 (last correction 1956), 2687; blad
              - 740: Achra River to Cape Ramas, 2nd February 1858 (last correction 1955), 2688; blad
              - 744: Cape Ramas to Alvagudda, 8th July 1858 (last correction 1955), 2689; blad
              - 745: Netrani to Mangalore, 31st October 1902 (last correction 1956), 2690; blad
              - 746: Mulki to Mount Delly, 21st August 1858 (last correction 1956), 2691; blad
              - 747: Mount Delly to Calicut, 2nd February 1859 (last correction 1954), 2692; blad
              - 749: Malabar coast from 11º 2' to 9º 50' N., 10th October 1857 (last correction 1954), 2693; blad
              - 750: Malabar coast from 9º 53'to 8º 40' N., 29th September 1857 (last correction 1953), 2694; blad
              - 751: Anjengo to Cape Comorin, 8th September 1857 (last correction 1949), 2695; blad
              - 813: Ceylon - south part, 13th November 1911 (last correction 1959), 2696; blad
              - 815: Approaches to Trincomalee, 2nd May 1947, 2697; blad
              - 815: Approaches to Trincomalee, 2nd May 1947 (last correction 1957), 2698; blad
              - 816: Trincomali Harbour, 4th August 1908 (last correction 1947), 2699; blad
              - 816: Trincomali Harbour, 4th August 1908 (last correction 1957), 2700; blad
              - 819: Approaches to Galle Harbour, 22nd June 1908 (last correction 1939), 2701; blad
              - 826: Karachi to Vengurla, 15th February 1877 (last correction 1956), 2702; blad
              - 827: Vengurla to Cape Comorin, 15th February 1877 (last correction 1962), 2703; blad
              - 914: Colombo Harbour, 6th September 1907 (last correction 1958), 2704; blad
              - 1012: Arabian Sea, 21st July 1961, 2705; blad
              - 1318: Approaches to Kandla and Navlakhi, 3rd October 1952 (revised 1961) (last correction 1962), 2706; blad
              - 1321: Plans on the Kathiawar Coast, 10th December 1927 (revised 1966), 2707; blad
              - 1322: Cannanore and Tellicherry anchorages, 19th November 1934 (last correction 1954), 2708; blad
              - 1470: Verával to Dwárka, 2nd November 1956, 2709; blad
              - 1474: Kotada Bluff to Mángrol, 7th December 1962, 2710; blad
              - 1655: Approaches to Colombo, 7th August 1992, 2711; blad
              - 1779: Ports and anchorages on the Kathiawar Coast, 28th December 1929 (last correction 1956), 2712; blad
              - 2031: Ceylon - east coast, 23rd May 1888 (last correction 1956), 2713; blad
              - 2197: Point Pedro to Delft Island, 22nd January 1897 (last correction 1956), 2714; blad
              - 2621: Bombay Harbour, 1st July 1960, 2715; blad
              - 2736: Gulf of Cutch to Vijaydurg, 1st July 1915 (last correction 1955), 2716; blad
              - 2851: Masira to Ruus al Jibal, 9th May 1952, 2717; blad
              - 2869: Muscat and Al Matrah, 27th May 1862 (revised 1965) (last correction 1966), 2718; blad
              - 2898: Maldive Islands to Ceylon, 19th May 1944 (last correction 1951), 2719; blad
              - 3265: Galle Harbour to Little Basses Reef, 5th February 1960, 2720; blad
              - 3267: Malpe - Mangalore Harbour, 24th May 1963, 2721; blad
              - 3284: Salaya Harbour, 26th July 1902 (last correction 1944), 2722; blad
              - 3461: New Mangalore - Mangalore and their approaches with Quilon, Calicut and Beypore anchorages, 16th March 1990, 2723; blad
              - 3686: Approaches to Colombo Harbour, 17th March 1908 (last correction 1956), 2724; blad
              - 3700: Colombo to Galle, 5th February 1960, 2725; blad
              - 3784: Ras al Kalb to Marbat, 27th February 1931 (last correction 1953), 2726; blad
              - 3785: Marbat to Masira Island, 1st November 1930 (last correction 1952), 2727; blad
            - Bay of Bengal, B.2.7.3.2.2.2
              - 67: Turicorin roadstead and harbour, 23rd April 1881 (last correction 1950), 2728; blad
              - 70: Bay of Bengal, 30th August 1963 (last correction 1967), 2729; blad
              - 71: Madras to Calimere Point, 17th September 1902 (last correction 1962), 2730; blad
              - 84: Approches to Karnaphuli River, 24th August 1945 (last correction 1959), 2731; blad
              - 136: River Hooghly - Sagar Roads to Calcutta, 20th January 1950 (last correction 1956), 2732; blad
              - 136: River Hooghly - Saugor Roads to Calcutta, 20th January 1950 (revised 1960), 2733; blad
              - 216a: Loughborough Island to Mergui, 1st February 1830 (revised 1938) (last correction 1948), 2734; blad
              - 239: Approaches to Vishakhapatnam, 27th November 1981 (last correction 1992), 2735; blad
              - 574: Approaches to Madras, 1st July 1960, 2736; blad
              - 575: Madras to Ramayapatnam, 9th December 1895 (last correction 1956), 2737; blad
              - 732: Pussur River, 18th December 1953 (last correction 1958), 2738; blad
              - 732: Pussur River, 7th May 1965 (revised 1967), 2739; blad
              - 814: The Sandheads - False point to Matla River, 25th July 1878 (last correction 1962), 2740; blad
              - 821: Elephant Point to Chedúba Strait, 30th January 1874 (last correction 1956), 2741; blad
              - 823: Koronge Island to White Point, 15th December 1873 (last correction 1955), 2742; blad
              - 824: White Point to Mergui, 27th July 1922 (last correction 1955), 2743; blad
              - 825: Andaman Islands, 1st August 1891 (last correction 1955), 2744; blad
              - 828: Cape Comorin to Cocanada, 8th May 1877 (last correction 1961), 2745; blad
              - 829: Cocanada to Bassein River, 22nd August 1877 (revised 1959) (last correction 1965), 2746; blad
              - 830: Bassein River to Pulo Penang, including the Andaman and Nicobar Islands, 20th October 1877 (last correction 1955), 2747; blad
              - 830: Bassein River to Pulo Penang, including the Andaman and Nicobar Islands, 20th October 1877 (last correction 1960), 2748; blad
              - 831: Kyauk Pyu Harbour to Chedúba Strait, 11th December 1912 (last correction 1956), 2749; blad
              - 832: Chedúba Strait and Ramree Harbour, 9th July 1887 (last correction 1953), 2750; blad
              - 833: Rangoon River and approaches, 1st May 1953 (revised 1961), 2751; blad
              - 834: Bassein River and approaches, 19th April 1892 (revised 1967), 2752; blad
              - 840: Nicobar Islands, 8th May 1959, 2753; blad
              - 842: Similan Islands to Pulau Langkawi, 30th January 1879 (last correction 1947), 2754; blad
              - 859: Matla River to Elephant Point, 18th July 1880 (revised 1959) (last correction 1966), 2755; blad
              - 999: Mae Nam Chao Phraya from The Bar to Bangkok, 14th March 1934 (revised 1962) (last correction 1967), 2756; blad
              - 1140: Tanjong Sepat to Port Dickson, 27th July 1962, 2757; blad
              - 1272: Approaches to Yé River, 28th November 1889 (last correction 1948), 2758; blad
              - 1369: Mayu River to Kyaukpyu Harbour, 30th April 1913 (last correction 1956), 2759; blad
              - 1398: Port Blair to Little Andaman Island, 5th June 1890 (last correction 1954), 2760; blad
              - 1424: Bimlipatam to Gopalpur, 3rd December 1891 (last correction 1952), 2761; blad
              - 1425: Gopalpur to False Point, 8th November 1890 (last correction 1955), 2762; blad
              - 1425: Gopalpur to False Point, 8th November 1890 (last correction 1965), 2763; blad
              - 1646: Moulmein Harbour, 16th February 1962, 2764; blad
              - 1711: Narasapur Point to Bimlipatam, 6th March 1893 (last correction 1958), 2765; blad
              - 1845: Moulmein River and approaches, 1st June 1901 (revised 1966), 2766; blad
              - 1884: Kaladan River, 18th August 1848 (last correction 1955), 2767; blad
              - 1885: Akyab Harbour, 22nd July 1929 (last correction 1955), 2768; blad
              - 1894: Ramayapatnam to Narasapur Point, 2nd April 1894 (last correction 1954), 2769; blad
              - 2103: Sihanoukville, 10th March 1961, 2770; blad
              - 3051: Domel Island to Pakchan River, 30th June 1939 (last correction 1950), 2771; blad
              - 3052: St. Matthews Island to Similan Islands, 9th July 1948 (last correction 1956), 2772; blad
              - 3103: Northern part of north Andaman Island with adjacent channels, 12th January 1900 (last correction 1955), 2773; blad
              - 3481: Moulmein River to Ye River, 13th May 1905 (last correction 1953), 2774; blad
              - 3493: Cox's Bazar to Mayu River, 18th June 1906 (last correction 1948), 2775; blad
              - 3624: Pig Island to South Moskos Islands, 18th November 1918 (last correction 1946), 2776; blad
              - 3727: Approaches to Satahib Bay - Goh Sichang Harbour, 4th March 1940 (last correction 1954), 2777; blad
              - 3771: Andrew Bay to Calventuras, 12th June 1912 (last correction 1956), 2778; blad
              - 3772: Calventuras to Bassein River, 14th May 1912 (revised 1967), 2779; blad
              - 3941: Similan Islands to Ko Lanta Hyai, 26th August 1955 (last correction 1958), 2780; blad
              - 3942: Ko Lanta Huai to Ko Terutao, 2nd November 1956, 2781; blad
            - Coastal waters east coast Africa, including Madagascar and Mauritius, B.2.7.3.2.2.3
              - 3: Chagos Archipelago, 2nd December 1839 (last correction 1944), 2782; blad
              - 4: Principal groups of the Chagos Archipelago, published in September, 1881 (last correction 1940), 2783; blad
              - 66a: Maldive Islands (northern sheet), published in October, 1866 (last correction 1918), 2784; blad
              - 66b: Maldive Islands (middle sheet), published in October, 1866 (last correction 1942), 2785; blad
              - 66c: Maldive Islands (southern sheet), published in October, 1866 (last correction 1950), 2786; blad
              - 317: Ampamonti, Ampasindava and Andranoaombi Bays - anchorages on the coast of Madagascar, 13th May 1891 (last correction 1955), 2787; blad
              - 377: Moramba Bay to Maromanjo Point, 30th September 1895 (last correction 1954), 2788; blad
              - 492: Enseada da Agoada and Baia de Mormugao, 14th February 1884 (last correction 1955), 2789; blad
              - 492: Enseada da Agoada and Baia de Mormugao, 14th February 1884 (last correction 1943), 2790; blad
              - 563: Comoro, Mohilla and Anjouan Islands, 8th July 1895 (last correction 1943), 2791; blad
              - 563: Comoro, Mohilla and Anjouan Islands, 8th July 1895 (last correction 1951), 2792; blad
              - 577: Approaches to Durban, 6th May 1960, 2793; blad
              - 596: Cape of Good Hope to Beira including southern portion of Madagascar, 4th March 1935 (revised 1960), 2794; blad
              - 597: Moçambique Channel to Socotra, 23rd February 1962, 2795; blad
              - 597: Delagoa Bay to Cape Guardafu including Madagascar, 21st October 1882 (last correction 1955), 2796; blad
              - 616: Approaches to Mombasa, 3rd December 1948 (last correction 1964), 2797; blad
              - 639: Mossel Bay and Harbour, 7th November 1863 (last correction 1957), 2798; blad
              - 640a: Zanzibar Channel - southern sheet, 30th January 1875 (last correction 1957), 2799; blad
              - 640b: Zanzibar Channel - northern sheet, date unknown (last correction 1957), 2800; blad
              - 641: Approaches to Port Elizabeth, 31st December 1938 (revised 1959), 2801; blad
              - 642: Plans in Portuguese East Africa, 29th October 1954 (revised 1962), 2802; blad
              - 643: Durban, 29th May 1924 (revised 1963), 2803; blad
              - 644: Baia de Lourenço Marques, 16th January 1953 (revised 1961), 2804; blad
              - 646: Porto de Lourenço Marques, 18th May 1951 (revised 1961), 2805; blad
              - 647: Barra e Porto de Inhambane, 9th March 1956 (last correction 1961), 2806; blad
              - 648: Lourenço Marques to Porto de Bartolomeu Dias, 18th January 1963, 2807; blad
              - 649: Approaches to Porto de Nacala - Porto de Nacala, 28th December 1956 (last correction 1957), 2808; blad
              - 650: Porto de Quelimane, 9th March 1956 (last correction 1960), 2809; blad
              - 653: Mokambo, Mozambique and Conducia, 30th December 1938 (last correction 1952), 2810; blad
              - 661: Kilwa Kisiwani, 10th March 1879 (last correction 1950), 2811; blad
              - 662: Kilwa Point to Zanzibar Channel, 31st January 1876 (last correction 1954), 2812; blad
              - 663: Manza and Tanga Bays, 3rd December 1894 (last correction 1956), 2813; blad
              - 664: Zanzibar to Malindi, 25th February 1891 (revised 1959), 2814; blad
              - 665: Approaches to Zanzibar, 7th September 1956, 2815; blad
              - 666: Ports Mombasa, Kilindini and Reitz, 1st August 1944 (revised 1966) (last correction 1970), 2816; blad
              - 667: Port Malindi and approaches, 4th February 1891 (last correction 1963), 2817; blad
              - 668: Lamu, Manda and Pate Bays and approaches, 14th November 1980 (revised 1991), 2818; blad
              - 671: Plans on the coast of Somaliland, 27th January 1950 (last correction 1953), 2819; blad
              - 671: Plans on the coast of Somaliland, 27th January 1950 (last correction 1956), 2820; blad
              - 674: Approaches to Dar es Salaam, 5th March 1954 (last correction 1956), 2821; blad
              - 679: Anchorages on the east coast of Madagascar, 10th March 1933 (revised 1962), 2822; blad
              - 680: Anchorages on the east coast of Madagascar, 22nd November 1934 (revised 1959), 2823; blad
              - 680: Anchorages on the east coast of Madagascar, 22nd November 1934 (revised 1962), 2824; blad
              - 681: Lindi Bay and Harbour, 15th May 1875 (revised 1961), 2825; blad
              - 683: Ile and Port Ste. Marie, 24th August 1827 (last correction 1960), 2826; blad
              - 684: Mtwara and Mikindani harbours, 10th May 1875 (last correction 1961), 2827; blad
              - 687: Kiswere Harbour, 31st December 1874 (last correction 1961), 2828; blad
              - 688: Tamatave, 10th November 1902 (last correction 1957), 2829; blad
              - 691: Mtwara Harbour, 31st May 1948 (last correction 1961), 2830; blad
              - 692: St. Augustine and Tulléar Bays, 22nd July 1895 (last correction 1951), 2831; blad
              - 693: Dar es Salaam, 8th June 1951 (last correction 1956), 2832; blad
              - 701: Approaches to Baie de Bombetoke - Baie de Bombetoke, 1st March 1963, 2833; blad
              - 704: Nosi Shaba to Moramba Bay including Narendri Bay, 30th September 1895 (last correction 1956), 2834; blad
              - 706: Iles Mitsio to Baie d'Ampasindava, 10th December 1927 (last correction 1960), 2835; blad
              - 707: Ambavatobi Bay, 31st March 1905 (last correction 1954), 2836; blad
              - 709: Ujong Katiagan to Ujong Tanjung, 21st March 1899 (last correction 1959), 2837; blad
              - 711: Mauritius, 5th July 1879 (last correction 1955), 2838; blad